Board of Governors fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Agenda support papers, 1963 - 2003; F-33-2; 15.83 m of textual records
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). Aug. 14, 1978, F-33-2-0-0-409 (Archival box - standard 33-61)
  - Agenda support papers - Executive meeting. Sept. 6, 1978, F-33-2-0-0-410 (Archival box - standard 33-61)
  - Agenda support papers (special meetings). Sept. 18, 20, 1978, F-33-2-0-0-411 (Archival box - standard 33-61)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Sept. 1978, F-33-2-0-0-412 (Archival box - standard 33-62)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Sept. 1978, F-33-2-0-0-413 (Archival box - standard 33-62)
  - Agenda support papers. Oct. 1978, F-33-2-0-0-414 (Archival box - standard 33-62)
  - Agenda support papers - Executive meeting. Oct. 18, 1978, F-33-2-0-0-415 (Archival box - standard 33-62)
  - Agenda support papers. Nov. 1978, F-33-2-0-0-416 (Archival box - standard 33-62)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Jan. 1979, F-33-2-0-0-417 (Archival box - standard 33-62)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Jan. 1979, F-33-2-0-0-418 (Archival box - standard 33-63)
  - Agenda support papers. Feb. 1979, F-33-2-0-0-419 (Archival box - standard 33-63)
  - Agenda support papers. Mar. 1979, F-33-2-0-0-420 (Archival box - standard 33-63)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). Apr. 11, 1979, F-33-2-0-0-421 (Archival box - standard 33-63)
  - Agenda support papers. Apr. 1979, F-33-2-0-0-422 (Archival box - standard 33-63)
  - Agenda support papers. May 1979, F-33-2-0-0-423 (Archival box - standard 33-63)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. June 1979, F-33-2-0-0-424 (Archival box - standard 33-63)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. June 1979, F-33-2-0-0-425 (Archival box - standard 33-64)
  - Agenda support papers. July 1979, F-33-2-0-0-426 (Archival box - standard 33-64)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). Aug. 7, 1979, 1975 - 1979; F-33-2-0-0-427 (Archival box - standard 33-64)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). Sept. 18, 1979, F-33-2-0-0-428 (Archival box - standard 33-64)
  - Agenda support papers. Sept. 1979, F-33-2-0-0-429 (Archival box - standard 33-64)
  - Agenda support papers. Oct. 1979, F-33-2-0-0-430 (Archival box - standard 33-64)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Nov. 1979, F-33-2-0-0-431 (Archival box - standard 33-65)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Nov. 1979, F-33-2-0-0-432 (Archival box - standard 33-65)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Nov. 1979, F-33-2-0-0-433 (Archival box - standard 33-65)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). Dec. 18, 1979, F-33-2-0-0-434 (Archival box - standard 33-65)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Jan. 1980, F-33-2-0-0-435 (Archival box - standard 33-65)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Jan. 1980, F-33-2-0-0-436 (Archival box - standard 33-65)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Feb. 1980, F-33-2-0-0-437 (Archival box - standard 33-66)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Feb. 1980, F-33-2-0-0-438 (Archival box - standard 33-66)
  - Agenda support papers. Mar. 1980, F-33-2-0-0-439 (Archival box - standard 33-66)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Apr. 1980, F-33-2-0-0-440 (Archival box - standard 33-66)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Apr. 1980, F-33-2-0-0-441 (Archival box - standard 33-66)
  - Agenda support papers. May 1980, F-33-2-0-0-442 (Archival box - standard 33-66)
  - Agenda support papers. June 1980, F-33-2-0-0-443 (Archival box - standard 33-67)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. July 1980, F-33-2-0-0-444 (Archival box - standard 33-67)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. July 1980, F-33-2-0-0-445 (Archival box - standard 33-67)
  - Agenda support papers. Sept. 1980, F-33-2-0-0-446 (Archival box - standard 33-67)
  - Agenda support papers. Oct. 1980, F-33-2-0-0-447 (Archival box - standard 33-67)
  - Agenda support papers. Nov. 1980, F-33-2-0-0-448 (Archival box - standard 33-68)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Jan. 1981, F-33-2-0-0-449 (Archival box - standard 33-68)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Jan. 1981, F-33-2-0-0-450 (Archival box - standard 33-68)
  - Agenda support papers. Feb. 1981, F-33-2-0-0-451 (Archival box - standard 33-68)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). Mar. 3, 1981, F-33-2-0-0-452 (Archival box - standard 33-68)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Mar. 1981, F-33-2-0-0-453 (Archival box - standard 33-68)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Mar. 1981, F-33-2-0-0-454 (Archival box - standard 33-69)
  - Agenda support papers - Meeting appendices. Jan. 1981 - Oct. 1982, 1981 - 1982; F-33-2-0-0-455 (Archival box - standard 33-69)
  - Agenda support papers - Meeting appendices. Jan. 1981 - Oct. 1982, 1981 - 1982; F-33-2-0-0-456 (Archival box - standard 33-69)
  - Agenda support papers. Apr. 1981, F-33-2-0-0-457 (Archival box - standard 33-69)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. May 1981, F-33-2-0-0-458 (Archival box - standard 33-69)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. May 1981, F-33-2-0-0-459 (Archival box - standard 33-69)
  - Agenda support papers. June 1981, F-33-2-0-0-460 (Archival box - standard 33-70)
  - Agenda support papers. July 1981, F-33-2-0-0-461 (Archival box - standard 33-70)
  - Agenda support papers - Board information meeting 1/2. Sept. 15, 1981, F-33-2-0-0-462 (Archival box - standard 33-70)
  - Agenda support papers - Board information meeting 2/2. Sept. 15, 1981, F-33-2-0-0-463 (Archival box - standard 33-70)
  - Agenda support papers. Sept. 1981, F-33-2-0-0-464 (Archival box - standard 33-70)
  - Agenda support papers - Board and UCBC. Sept. 22, 1981, F-33-2-0-0-465 (Archival box - standard 33-70)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). Sept. 30, 1981, F-33-2-0-0-466 (Archival box - standard 33-70)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Oct. 1981, F-33-2-0-0-467 (Archival box - standard 33-71)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Oct. 1981, F-33-2-0-0-468 (Archival box - standard 33-71)
  - Agenda support papers. Nov. 1981, F-33-2-0-0-469 (Archival box - standard 33-71)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Jan. 1982, F-33-2-0-0-470 (Archival box - standard 33-71)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Jan. 1982, F-33-2-0-0-471 (Archival box - standard 33-71)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Jan. 1982, F-33-2-0-0-472 (Archival box - standard 33-71)
  - Agenda support papers - Budget Letters 1/2. Feb. 23, 1982, F-33-2-0-0-473 (Archival box - standard 33-72)
  - Agenda support papers - Budget Letters 2/2. Feb. 23, 1982, F-33-2-0-0-474 (Archival box - standard 33-72)
  - Agenda support papers. Feb. 1982, F-33-2-0-0-475 (Archival box - standard 33-72)
  - Agenda support papers. Mar. 1982, F-33-2-0-0-476 (Archival box - standard 33-72)
  - Agenda support papers. Apr. 1982, F-33-2-0-0-477 (Archival box - standard 33-72)
  - Agenda support papers. May 1982, F-33-2-0-0-478 (Archival box - standard 33-72)
  - Special Board meeting and Employee Relations Committee. May 11, 1982, F-33-2-0-0-479 (Archival box - standard 33-73)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. June 1982, F-33-2-0-0-480 (Archival box - standard 33-73)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. June 1982, F-33-2-0-0-481 (Archival box - standard 33-73)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. July 1982, F-33-2-0-0-482 (Archival box - standard 33-73)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. July 1982, F-33-2-0-0-483 (Archival box - standard 33-73)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Sept. 1982, F-33-2-0-0-484 (Archival box - standard 33-73)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Sept. 1982, F-33-2-0-0-485 (Archival box - standard 33-73)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Oct. 1982, F-33-2-0-0-486 (Archival box - standard 33-74)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Oct. 1982, F-33-2-0-0-487 (Archival box - standard 33-74)
  - Agenda support papers. Nov. 1982, F-33-2-0-0-488 (Archival box - standard 33-74)
- Policies and procedures, 1965 - 2003; F-33-3; 83 cm of textual records
  The Board of Governors approves all academic policies, most general policies unless they are procedures, and significant administrative policies. Series consists of policies and procedures and working files.
  The subseries 3-3 (Policy groups) was superceded in 2007 by individual subseries for each of the policy groups.
  - Early policies, 1965 - 1972; F-33-3-1; 3 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of an early set of policies and procedures relating to the President's Office, General Services, the Library, Purchasing, Personnel and the Registrar's Office.
    Access may be restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
    - President's Office, 1966 - 1972; F-33-3-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - General Services, 1965 - 1968; F-33-3-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - Library, 1968; F-33-3-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - Purchasing, 1966; F-33-3-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - Personnel, 1966; F-33-3-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - Registrar, 1966; F-33-3-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
  - Policy working files, 1968 - 1990; F-33-3-2; 24 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of working files relating to the development of policy groups: GP (General), AC (Academic), and AD (Administrative). Includes drafts, memos and other documents.
    - GP 1 - Acting Administrators, 1972 - 1977; F-33-3-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - GP 2 - Political leave, 1973; F-33-3-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - GP 3 - Donations, 1974; F-33-3-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - GP 5 - Strike policy, 1975 - 1979; F-33-3-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - GP 7 - Word processing, 1977 - 1979; F-33-3-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - GP 9 - Relocation expenses, 1980 - 1990; F-33-3-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - GP 10 - Special fees, 1980 - 1981; F-33-3-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - GP 11 - Policy for Images theatre, 1980 - 1981; F-33-3-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - GP 16 - Smoking policy, 1987 - 1989; F-33-3-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - Index - academic policies, 1989 - 1990; F-33-3-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - AC 1 - Academic appointments Rev. A, 1969 - 1970; F-33-3-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - AC 1 - Academic appointments Rev. B, 1977 - 1988; F-33-3-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - AC 2 - Academic freedom and tenure, 1968 - 1973; F-33-3-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - AC 2 - Renewal, tenure and promotion, 1972 - 1978; F-33-3-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
      Open
      Reviewed for access (Apr 2023): no restricted information identified.
    - AC 3 - University copyright policy, 1969 - 1985; F-33-3-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - AC 5 - Academic operating budget, 1969 - 1975; F-33-3-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - AC 6 - Sessional lecturers/instructors, 1969 - 1978; F-33-3-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - AC 7 - Patent policy, 1969 - 1975; F-33-3-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - AC 8 - Leave of absence, 1968 - 1979; F-33-3-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - AC 9 - Research associates, 1969; F-33-3-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - AC 11 - Resignations, 1969; F-33-3-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - AC 12 - Visiting faculty and limited term faculty appointments, 1970 - 1985; F-33-3-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 33-75)
    - AC 13 - Requests for capital expenditures, 1970; F-33-3-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 33-76)
    - AC 16 - Appointment of part time faculty, 1971 - 1986; F-33-3-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 33-76)
    - AC 18 - Laboratory instructors I and II, 1976 - 1988; F-33-3-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 33-76)
    - AC 19 - Sabbatical leave, 1971 - 1977; F-33-3-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 33-76)
    - AC 20 - Faculty association and program coordinators in the Faculty of Education, 1971 - 1988; F-33-3-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 33-76)
    - AC 22 - Faculty salaries, 1972 - 1988; F-33-3-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 33-76)
    - AC 23 - Lecturers, 1973 - 1989; F-33-3-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 33-76)
      Open, no restrictions
      Access review (May 18, 2023) – File is open, no restricted information identified.
    - AC 26 - Hiring policy, academic appointments, 1973 - 1975; F-33-3-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 33-76)
    - AC 27 - External research grants and contracts, 1975 - 1982; F-33-3-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 33-76)
    - AC 32 - Sessional lecturers, 1977 - 1989; F-33-3-2-0-32 (Archival box - standard 33-76)
    - AC 33 - Strike policy, 1978; F-33-3-2-0-33 (Archival box - standard 33-76)
    - AC 35 - Research and study groups, 1979; F-33-3-2-0-34 (Archival box - standard 33-76)
    - AC 36 - Treatment of animals used in research and teaching at SFU, 1979 - 1987; F-33-3-2-0-35 (Archival box - standard 33-76)
    - AC 43 - Research professors, 1980 - 1982; F-33-3-2-0-36 (Archival box - standard 33-76)
    - AC 45 - Professional librarians, 1981; F-33-3-2-0-37 (Archival box - standard 33-76)
    - AC 46 - Faculty workload, 1981 - 1988; F-33-3-2-0-38 (Archival box - standard 33-76)
    - AC 49 - Statement on intellectual honesty, 1981 - 1982; F-33-3-2-0-39 (Archival box - standard 33-76)
    - AC 50 - Procedures for dealing with incidents of intellectual dishonesty, 1981; F-33-3-2-0-40 (Archival box - standard 33-76)
    - AC 51 - Terms of reference, Senate committee on academic discipline, 1981 - 1982; F-33-3-2-0-41 (Archival box - standard 33-76)
    - AD 3 - Bursar, 1969 - 1978; F-33-3-2-0-42 (Archival box - standard 33-76)
    - AD 9 - Personnel, 1976 - 1977; F-33-3-2-0-43 (Archival box - standard 33-76)
    - Gym Services for Transsexuals, 1981; F-33-3-2-0-44 (Archival box - standard 33-80)
    - AC 30 Adjunct Professors, 1977; F-33-3-2-0-45 (Archival box - standard 33-76)
  - AC policies, 1968 - 1995; F-33-3-4; 6 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of AC series policies and their revisions over time. In 1992, the AC policy series were replaced by policy series A, R and T.
    The files are open with no restrictions.
    - AC Series policy list, 1978 - 1995; F-33-3-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-1.
    - AC 1 Academic appointments, 1969 - 1992; F-33-3-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-2.
    - AC 2 Renewal, tenure and promotion, 1975 - 1991; F-33-3-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-3.
    - AC 3 University copyright policy, 1975 - 1986; F-33-3-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-4.
    - AC 4 Graduate Associates, 1969; F-33-3-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-5.
    - AC 5 Academic operating budget, 1975 - 1978; F-33-3-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-6.
    - AC 6 Sessional lecturers/instructors, 1973 - 1980; F-33-3-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-7.
    - AC 7 Patent policy, 1975; F-33-3-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-8.
    - AC 8 Leave of absence, 1968 - 1985; F-33-3-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-9.
    - AC 9 University research associate, 1969 - 1992; F-33-3-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-10.
    - AC 10 Trimester operation, 1969 - 1987; F-33-3-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-11.
    - AC 11 Resignations, 1969 - 1978; F-33-3-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-12.
    - AC 12 Visiting faculty and limited term faculty appointments, 1970 - 1985; F-33-3-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-13.
    - AC 13 Requests for capital expenditures, 1970; F-33-3-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-14.
    - AC 14 Retirement date - faculty members and professional librarians, 1971; F-33-3-4-0-15 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-15.
    - AC 15 Appointment of retired faculty, lecturers, laboratory instructors, librarians and archivists, 1971 - 1991; F-33-3-4-0-16 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-16.
    - AC 16 Appointment of part time faculty, 1971 - 1986; F-33-3-4-0-17 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-17.
    - AC 17 Appointment of lecturers in continuing education: short term, 1971; F-33-3-4-0-18 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-18.
    - AC 18 Laboratory instructors I and II, 1971 - 1991; F-33-3-4-0-19 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-19.
    - AC 19 Sabbatical leave, 1975 - 1991; F-33-3-4-0-20 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-20.
    - AC 20 Faculty associates and program coordinators in the Faculty of Education, 1975 - 1988; F-33-3-4-0-21 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-21.
    - AC 21 Releasing of research equipment when faculty members resign, 1972; F-33-3-4-0-22 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-22.
    - AC 22 Faculty salaries, 1974 - 1992; F-33-3-4-0-23 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-23.
    - AC 23 Lecturers and senior lecturers, 1974 - 1987; F-33-3-4-0-24 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-24.
    - AC 24 Payment of stipends for teaching, 1973; F-33-3-4-0-25 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-25.
    - AC 25 Medical leave and long term disability, 1973 - 1986; F-33-3-4-0-26 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-26.
    - AC 26 Hiring policy, academic appointments, 1975 - 1977; F-33-3-4-0-27 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-27.
    - AC 27 External research grants and contracts, 1975 - 1986; F-33-3-4-0-28 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-28.
    - AC 28 Teaching assistants, 1977; F-33-3-4-0-29 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-29.
    - AC 29 Associate members, 1977; F-33-3-4-0-30 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-30.
    - AC 30 Adjunct professors, 1977 - 1982; F-33-3-4-0-31 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-31.
    - AC 31 Statement of faculty responsibilities, 1977 - 1989; F-33-3-4-0-32 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-32.
    - AC 32 Sessional lecturers, 1978 - 1990; F-33-3-4-0-33 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-33.
    - AC 33 Strike policy, 1978 - 1981; F-33-3-4-0-34 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-34.
    - AC 34 Relocation expenses for tenure track faculty, 1978 - 1992; F-33-3-4-0-35 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-35.
    - AC 35 Research and study groups, centres and institutes, 1979 - 1992; F-33-3-4-0-36 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-36.
    - AC 36 Treatment of animals used in research and teaching at SFU, 1979 - 1987; F-33-3-4-0-37 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-37.
    - AC 37 Maternity leave, 1979; F-33-3-4-0-38 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-38.
    - AC 38 Faculty exchanges, 1979; F-33-3-4-0-39 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-39.
    - AC 39 Policy guidelines for grading practices, 1979 - 1981; F-33-3-4-0-40 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-40.
    - AC 41 Dismissal procedure - faculty, 1974; F-33-3-4-0-41 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-41.
    - AC 42 Professors emeriti/ae, 1978 - 1987; F-33-3-4-0-42 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-42.
    - AC 43 Research professors, 1980 - 1982; F-33-3-4-0-43 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-43.
    - AC 44 Terms of appointment for academic administrators, 1980 - 1990; F-33-3-4-0-44 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-44.
    - AC 45 Professional librarians, 1981 - 1991; F-33-3-4-0-45 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-45.
    - AC 46 Faculty workload, 1981 - 1983; F-33-3-4-0-46 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-46.
    - AC 47 NSERC University research fellows, 1982; F-33-3-4-0-47 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-47.
    - AC 48 Code of faculty ethics and responsibilities, 1982; F-33-3-4-0-48 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-48.
    - AC 49 Statement on intellectual honesty, 1981; F-33-3-4-0-49 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-49.
    - AC 50 Dealing with incidents of intellectual dishonesty, 1981; F-33-3-4-0-50 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-50.
    - AC 51 Terms of reference, Senate committee on academic discipline, 1981 - 1988; F-33-3-4-0-51 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-51.
    - AC 52 Statement on student conduct, 1981; F-33-3-4-0-52 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-52.
    - AC 53 Joint appointments, 1983; F-33-3-4-0-53 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-53.
    - AC 54 Benefits for SFUFA bargaining unit members, retirees and visiting faculty, 1985 - 1992; F-33-3-4-0-54 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-54.
    - AC 55 Limited term lecturers, 1987 - 1990; F-33-3-4-0-55 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-55.
    - AC 56 Mortgage assistance program, 1990 - 1991; F-33-3-4-0-56 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-56.
    - AC 57 Appointment of department chairs and directors of schools, 1991; F-33-3-4-0-57 (Archival box - standard 33-77)
  - Academic policies (A series), 1992 - 2003; F-33-3-5; 6 cm of textual records